export default QuestionsData = [
    { Title: 'A Letter to God', Description: 'A Letter to God Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of A Letter to God?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option A' },
    { Title: 'Nelson Mandela Long Walk to Freedom', Description: 'Nelson Mandela Long Walk to Freedom Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of Nelson Mandela Long Walk to Freedom?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option B' },
    { Title: 'Two Stories About Flying', Description: 'Two Stories About Flying Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of Two Stories About Flying?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option C' },
    { Title: 'From the Diary of Anne Frank', Description: 'From the Diary of Anne Frank Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of From the Diary of Anne Frank?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option D' },
    { Title: 'Glimpses of India', Description: 'Glimpses of India Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of Glimpses of India?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option A' },
    { Title: 'Mijbil the Otter', Description: 'Mijbil the Otter Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of Mijbil the Otter?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option B' },
    { Title: 'Madam Rides the Bus', Description: 'Madam Rides the Bus Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of Madam Rides the Bus?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option C' },
    { Title: 'The Sermon at Benares', Description: 'The Sermon at Benares Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of The Sermon at Benares?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option D' },
    { Title: 'The Proposal', Description: 'The Proposal Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of The Proposal?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option A' },
    { Title: 'A Triumph of Surgery', Description: 'A Triumph of Surgery Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of A Triumph of Surgery?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option B' },
    { Title: 'The Thief’s Story', Description: 'The Thief’s Story Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of The Thief’s Story?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option C' },
    { Title: 'The Midnight Visitor', Description: 'The Midnight Visitor Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of The Midnight Visitor?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option D' },
    { Title: 'A Question of Trust', Description: 'A Question of Trust Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of A Question of Trust?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option A' },
    { Title: 'Footprints without Feet', Description: 'Footprints without Feet Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of Footprints without Feet?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option B' },
    { Title: 'The Making of a Scientist', Description: 'The Making of a Scientist Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of The Making of a Scientist?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option C' },
    { Title: 'The Necklace', Description: 'The Necklace Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of The Necklace?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option D' },
    { Title: 'Bholi', Description: 'Bholi Description', Question: 'Who is the writer of Bholi?', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option A' },
    { Title: 'The Book That Saved the Earth', Question: 'Who is the writer of The Book That Saved the Earth?', Description: 'The Book That Saved the Earth Description', options: [{ a: "This is Option A", b: "This is Option B", c: "This is Option C", d: "This is Option D" }], correctAns: 'This is Option B' },
]